你以为我看一眼恶魔
You think i'll take one look at a demon.
就会突然忘乎所以了
And suddenly fall off the wagon,
好像经过了那么多事我还没得到教训似的
As if, after everything, i haven't learned my lesson.
难道不是吗
Well, have you.
这是我女朋友 杰西卡
This is my girlfriend, jessica.
不！杰西卡！
No! jess!
下一步你怎么说
So, what are you gonna do.
你希望过着普通人般的生活
You just gonna live some normal, apple-pie life.
不是普通 是安全
Not normal. safe.
我是一具皮囊
I'm a vessel.
你是一具皮囊 米伽勒的皮囊
You're the vessel. michael's vessel.
这绝不可能
The answer's no.
卡西迪奥在哪里
Where's cass.
大天使长会杀死那个背叛者
The archangel smote the crap out of him.
你怎么会…
How are you…
还活着
Alive.
这个问题非常好
That's a good question.
我希望我可以像以前那样拯救苍生
I just wish I could save people, like I used to.
你意思说你想继续吸食恶魔血液
What … you mean when you were all hopped up on demon blood.
你打算杀了路西法
Your plan to kill lucifer.
这很愚蠢 那根本没用
It's foolish. it can't be done.
我找到了解决之道
I have the solution.
我要找到上帝
I'm gonna find god.
不如去新墨西哥洲找找 听说他幻化成墨西哥薄饼神了
Try new mexico. I hear he's on a tortilla.
这星期我已经杀了俩天使了
I killed two angels this week.
我成了背叛者 这一切 都是拜你所赐
I rebelled. and I did it … all of it … for you.
全因为你的过失所致
And you failed.
我无法继续猎杀恶魔了
I'm in no shape to be hunting.
可能的话我们最好分开行动
Maybe it's best we just go our separate ways.
你说的没错
Well, i think you're right.
嘿 宝贝
Hey, baby.
我很想你
I missed you.
杰西卡
Jessica.
我是在做梦吧
I'm dreaming.
你答错了
Or you're not.
我在这儿有区别么
What's the difference i'm here.
我想死你了
I miss you so much.
我了解
I know.
我也想你
I miss you, too.
你在做什么 萨姆
What are you doing, sam.
你指什么
What do you mean.
逃避
Running away.
我们可没有分手
Haven't we been down this road before.
当然没有
No.
不过今非昔比
It's different now.
真的吗
Really.
以前我只想回到正常人的生活
Last time, i wanted to be normal.
现在我明白自己是个怪物
This time… I know i'm a freak.
这只是文字游戏
Which is all a big ball of semantics.
你是知道的
You know that.
我不明白
No.
在斯坦福大学的时候你就知道了
Even at stanford, you knew.
你明白身体里有某种邪恶的力量
You knew there was something dark inside of you.
事实上 也许你一开始就知道
Deep down, maybe, but…you knew.
宝贝 那个东西杀了我
Baby, that's what got me killed.
不是这样的
No.
我们刚打完招呼 我就挂了
I was dead from the moment we said hello.
不
No.
其实你不懂
Don't you get it.
你无法摆脱自己
You can't run from yourself.
你在逃避什么
Why are you running now.
为什么你在这里 杰西卡
Why are you here, jess.
你相不相信我是在保护你
Would you believe i'm actually trying to protect you.
为了什么
From what.
为了你
You.
过去的阴影迟早会笼罩你
Sooner or later, the past is gonna catch up to you,
和过去一样
Like it always does.
你明白会发生什么
You know what happens then.
人们逐渐死去
People die.
宝贝 他们的死和你密切相关
Baby, the people closest to you die.
好吧 别担心 我不会重蹈覆辙
Well, don't worry, because I won't make that mistake again.
同样的歌 不同的调
Same song, different verse.
你并没有因此而改变
Things are never gonna change with you.
从来没有
Ever.
[邪恶力量 第5季第3集]
你好 我是比尔·巴克纳探长
Hi, i'm detective bill buckner.
我能帮你点什么 探长
Yes how can I help you, detective.
关于那些贫血患者
I'm here about those patients … the exsanguinated ones.
吃吧 你快死了
Eat it, twilight.
老天！
God!
别这样
Don't do that.
你好呀 迪恩
Hello, Dean.
卡西…
Cass…
我们商量好的
We've talked about this.
留点私人空间
Personal space.
我道歉
My apologies.
你怎么找到我的
How'd you find me.
我以为自己屏蔽了天使雷达网了呢
I thought I was flying below the angel radar.
没错
You are.
是鲍比告诉我你在这儿的
Bobby told me where you were.
萨姆呢？
Where's Sam.
我和萨姆要暂时分开一阵
Me and Sam are taking separate vacations for a while.
那…你找到上帝了吗？
So… did you find god yet.
我更关心的是我啥时能要回我的项链呀
More importantly, can I have my damn necklace back, please.
不 我还没找到他
No, i haven't found him.
所以我才来找你 我需要你帮忙
That's why i'm here. I need your help.
干嘛？一起寻找上帝吗？
With what … a god hunt.
我才没有兴趣
I'm not interested.
不是指上帝 而是其他人
It's not god. it's someone else.
谁
Who.
是大天使之一
It's an archangel.
就是他杀死了我
The one who killed me.
你说什么
Excuse me.
他的名字是拉斐尔
His name is raphael.
你被一个忍者神龟天使给废了？
You were wasted by a teenage mutant ninja angel.
我从天上听说他正在人间
I've heard whispers that he's walking the earth.
这下机会难得
This is a rare opportunity.
找他干嘛？为了复仇吗？
For what … revenge.
是为了获取情报
Information.
你是说 等你找到那家伙
So, what … you think if you find this dude,
就能套出上帝的住址了吗？
He's just gonna spill god's address.
是的
Yes.
因为我们要困住他后来审问
Because we are gonna trap him and interrogate him.
你是认真的吗
You're serious about this.
是的
Yes.
那我们就是末路狂花组合
So, what … i'm thelma and you're louise,
赤手空拳地
And we're just gonna hold hands.
去怒海争锋吗
And sail off this cliff together.
我为什么要帮你 给我个理由
Give me one good reason why I should do this.
因为你是米迦勒的皮囊
Because you're michael's vessel,
天使不敢伤害你
And no angel will dare harm you.
把我当成你的挡箭牌吗？
Oh, so i'm your bullet shield.
我需要你的帮助…
I need your help…
因为只有你肯帮我
Because you are the only one who will help me.
求你了
Please.
那好吧
All right. fine.
他在哪儿？
Where is he.
缅因州
Maine.
我们走
Let's go.
怎么了
What.
上次你把我瞬移到某个地方后
Last time you zapped me someplace,
害得我便秘了一个星期
I didn't poop for a week.
我们开车去
We're driving.
嘿 凯斯 你来玩吗
Hey, Keith, you play.
要看我们赌什么
That depends … what are we playing for.
为世界和平
World peace.
就这样吗？
Oh, is that all.
能问你个事儿吗？
Can I ask you something.
问吧
Shoot.
是你做完厨房里的填字游戏的吗？
You finish that, uh, crossword puzzle in the kitchen.
我想是吧 怎么了？
Uh, i-i guess. why.
那可是纽约时报周六版的填字游戏啊
The new york times saturday crossword.
真的吗
Was it.
上周你突然出现在这个小镇里不和任何人说话
You blow into town last week. you don't talk to anybody.
在我看你显然是受过高等教育
You're obviously highly educated.
- 你简直就像是… - 散发神秘气息
- You're like this… - Riddle wrapped.
的谜一般的人物吗？
Inside an enigma wra.
我们现在来赌这个
Here's what we play for.
我赢的话 你就请我吃晚饭 并告诉我有关你的事
When I win, you buy me dinner and tell me your life story.
听起来挺不错
Sounds fair.
你真是太神秘了
Very misterioso.
异物冰雹 闪电袭击
Freak hail, lightning strikes …
- 我喜欢 - 目前哈雷镇
- I like it. - Now fire consuming the.
正遭受大伙侵袭
Town of hawley.
据当地居民称 傍晚时分
Locals say what started as a torrential hailstorm.
起先是出现暴雨冰雹
Late this afternoon.
之后骤然突现剧烈闪电袭击
Suddenly turned to massive lightning strikes.
闪电引起的森林大火 现已蔓延20英亩
That triggered the fire now consuming more than 20 acres.
正沿着17号公路肆虐
Here along the route 17 corridor.
郡政府建议哈雷镇全体居民
County officials are advising all hawley residents.
做好准备以应对可能的强制疏散
To prepare for what could become mandatory evacuations.
见鬼
Damn.
就像世界末日到了
Is it me, or does it seem like the end of the world.
就是这儿
We're here why.
一个县副治安官见过天使长
A deputy sheriff laid eyes on the archangel.
他没失明吗
And he still has eyes.
好的 计划是什么
All right, what's the plan.
我们
We…
告诉那位官员 他见到了主的使者
Tell the officer that he witnessed an angel of the lord.
然后那位官员告诉我们天使长在哪里
Then the officer will tell us where the angel is.
你真的要这么做
Are you serious.
你走进去告诉他真相
You're gonna walk in there and tell him the truth.
为什么不呢
Why not.
因为 我们是凡人
Because… we're humans.
如果凡人们想干些非常坏的事情
And when humans want something really, really bad…
我们就撒谎
We lie.
为什么
Why.
因为 这样你才能当上总统
Because…that's how you become president.
弗明汉副官
Deputy Framingham.
阿朗佐·莫斯利 联邦调查局的
Alonzo Mosely, FBI.
这位是我的搭档 埃迪·莫斯康
This is my partner, Eddie Moscone.
也是联邦调查局的
Also FBI.
他是新手
He's, uh, he's new.
不介意我们问你几个问题吧
Mind if we ask you a few questions.
可以 到这里谈吧
Yeah. sure. talk here, though.
耳朵几乎都快听不到东西了
Hearing's all blown to hell in this one.
刚刚有事故？
That happen recently.
是的 加油站的事
Yeah … the gas-station thing.
所以你们才会来 不是吗
That's why you're here, isn't it.
是的
Yes, it is.
你不介意把刚才发生的事讲给我们吧
Do you mind just, uh, running us through what happened.
接到报警电话
Well, call came in …
四号公路的加油站外有骚乱
Disturbance out at the pump 'n' go on route 4.
什么样的骚乱
What kind of disturbance.
如果不是亲眼所见
Would not have believed my eyes.
我是不会相信眼前发生的一切
If I hadn't seen it myself.
我说的是暴乱 一场大规模的
We're talking a riot … full-scale.
- 多少人 - 30 40
- How many? - 30, 40.
所有的人 相互杀戮
In all-out, kill-or-be-killed combat.
是什么让他们发生冲突
Any idea what set them off.
很可能是天使和恶魔们
It's angels and demons, probably.
他们在世界上经常开战
They're skirmishing all over the globe.
他讲的什么 我没听明白
Come again what did he say.
- 恶魔们 - 没什么
- Demons. - Nothing.
心魔 你知道的 嗜酒 奸淫
Demons, you know … drink, adultery.
我们都有自己的心魔 沃尔特
We all have our demons, Walt. right.
我猜也是
I guess.
不管怎样 接下来发生了什么
Anyway… what happened next.
怪异的爆炸 那是
Freakin' explosion, that's what.
他们说是地下的一个汽油灌
Oh, they said it was one of those underground gas tanks,
但我不这么认为
But, uh… I don't think so.
为什么
Why not.
那不是普通的火球 那是…
It wasn't your usual fireball. it was, um…
纯白的
Pure white.
对
Yeah.
加油站在地面上
Gas station was leveled.
每个人都…
Everyone was…
那真是太可怕了
It was just horrible.
然后我看到有一个人跪在那里
Then I see this one guy, kneeling there,
那么的聚精会神
Real focused-like.
他身上没有一点伤
Not a damn scratch on him.
你认识他
You know him.
唐尼·芬尼曼 那里的机械师
Donnie Finnerman … mechanic there.
让我猜猜
And let me guess …
他随后就消失了
He just, uh… vanished into thin air.
没有
Uh, no, kolchak.
他在圣彼得医院
He's down at st. pete's.
圣彼得医院
St. pete's.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我猜他不是拉斐尔了
I take it that's not raphael anymore.
只是一副空皮囊
Just an empty vessel.
那么米迦勒从我身体出来后
So, is this what I'm looking at.
我也是这幅德行了
When michael jumps my bones.
不 一点也不是
No, not at all.
米迦勒的力量更强
Michael is much more powerful.
它对你将会更糟
It'll be far worse for you.
启示录
The Book of Revelation.
萨姆
Sam.
鲍比 你还好吗
Hey, bobby. how you doin'
我没有去跑马拉松
Well, I aren't runnin' any marathons, but…
可我还活着
I'll live.
你在哪
Where are you?
加伯 俄克拉荷马州
Uh, garber, oklahoma.
我发现有个镇上出现了启示
I found a town up the road showing some revelation omens.
什么征兆
What omens.
好吧 听这个
All right, listen to this.
在他到来之后
And upon his rising,
将会有冰雹与大火并带着鲜血
There shall be hail and fire mixed with blood.
听着可不怎么令人愉快
Well, ain't that delightful.
是啊
Yeah.
刚发生过雹灾和火灾
We already got hailstorms and fires.
我猜鲜血不久就会来到
I'm guessing blood can't be too far behind.
好的
Okay.
什么
What.
你打来就是为了这事
There a reason you're calling.
迪恩没跟你说吗
Dean didn't tell you.
他跟我说了
He told me.
哦 我想你应该知道
Yeah, well… so I just thought.
哪些猎人
You might want to find out who's in the area,
熟悉这个地方的
Put a man on this.
好吧 我看看能不能找到
Okay, let me see if I can think.
就近的最好的猎人
Of the best hunter who might be in the immediate vicinity.
就是你了
Oh … that'd be you.
我不行 鲍比 我不参与这些事了
I can't, Bobby. I'm sitting this one out.
- 萨姆 - 我挂了
- Sam … - I got to go.
- 抱歉 - 等等 萨姆
- I'm so sorry. - Hold on. sam.
你去哪儿了
Where have you been.
耶路撒冷
Jerusalem.
是吗 那里怎样
Oh. How was it.
干旱
Arid.
这是什么
What is that.
油
It's oil.
这油很独特 珍稀少有
It's very special and very rare.
我们就用这瓶香料油来抓拉斐尔啰
Okay, are we gonna…trap Raphael with a nice vinaigrette.
不是
No.
那你们这仪式什么时候开始
So, this ritual of yours, when's it got to go down.
日出时
Sunrise.
告诉我 你一直说抓住个家伙
Tell me something … you keep saying we're gonna trap this guy.
不是一招半式
But isn't that kind of like.
就能抓到的
Trapping a hurricane with a butterfly net.
是的 这次更难
No. It's harder.
有活命的机会没
Do we have any chance of surviving this.
你有
You do.
就是说 今天是你最后一晚了
So, odds are, you're a dead man tomorrow.
对
Yes.
在地球上的最后一夜
Well, last night on earth.
你有什么打算
What, uh… what are your plans.
静静地坐在这里
I just thought I'd sit here quietly.
老兄 说吧 任何事都可以
Dude. Come on. Anything.
女人 花天酒地
Hmm booze, women.
你以前有跟女人交往过 对吧
You have been with a woman before, right.
至少跟天使有过
Or an angel, at least.
你不会想说 你还没有
You mean to tell me you've never been up there.
做过一次吧
Doing a little cloud-seeding.
我根本没那闲功夫 好吗
Look, I've never had occasion, okay.
好吧
All right.
我说吧
Let me tell you something.
有两件事我置信不疑
There are two things that I know for certain.
一 伯特和厄尼是同性恋（美动画片《芝麻街》两主角）
One, Bert and Ernie are gay.
二 你死之前得享受一次人间性福
Two, you are not gonna die a virgin.
我不关心这个
Not on my watch.
走吧
Let's go.
你好啊 萨姆
Hey, Sam.
萨姆
Sam!
- 萨姆 - 凯斯怎么回事
- Sam. - What happened to Keith?
什么
W-what.
他叫你萨姆
He called you Sam.
是 萨姆是我的中名
Yeah, uh… Sam's my middle name.
凯斯 萨姆
Keith Sam.
真抱歉啊
Man, I'm sorry.
其实是叫萨姆埃尔
Well, actually, it's, uh, Samuel,
就不像听起来那么蠢了
So it's not quite as dumb as it sounds.
你们是朋友吗
Are you guys friends.
跟他老爸一起打猎的
Huntin' buddies with his dad.
不过萨姆埃尔已经是独自打猎的高手了
But Samuel here is quite the hunter himself.
你捕杀鹿之类的动物吗
You kill deer and things.
是的 是那类的
Yeah, and things.
我们不妨去喝一杯吧
Uh, why don't I get you guys some drinks.
抱歉这么冒然来打扰你了
Sorry. Didn't mean to bust you back there.
不会 没关系
No, it, uh, it's all right.
说正事吧
So, what's up.
鲍比电话我了
Well, Bobby called.
然后呢
And.
你说对了
You were right …
大部分恶魔都过来聚会了
Major demon block party going on.
但他们为什么原因来了
But why what are they up to.
还不知道
Don't know yet.
鲍比说 你已经不参与此事了
Bobby told us you were off limits.
是真的吗
That true.
对 是真的
Yeah, that's right.
照理说 这没关系
Well, that's fine in theory and all,
但是我们现在必须召集足够人手
But we could really use all hands on deck here.
你们能行的
I know you could.
但别算我 抱歉
But I can't. I'm sorry.
为什么不行呢
Why not.
是私事
It's personal.
听着萨姆 无意冒犯 到底是什么负担这么重
Look, Sam, no offense, but, uh, what baggage is so heavy,
甚至让你无视该死的天启的活
It can't be stowed away for the freakin' apocalypse, huh.
我说了
Like I said…
对
Yeah.
你很抱歉
You're sorry.
第一句话就说了这个
Heard you the first time.
好吧
Okay.
随便你
Suit yourself.
接着还有更多我们要做的
More for us, then, right.
祝好运
Good luck.
不过等我们回来的时候啤酒你得准备好
But, hey … beers are on you when we get back.
那当然
Yeah, you bet.
你父母指定你去猎小鹿的时候喝醉了
So, your parents were drunk when they named you,
然后你向小鹿斑比抬起了枪
And you shoot bambi.
这个说来话长
I-it's a…long story.
换句话说
That is it.
你有足够的野外生存经验
Enough with the kung-fu, wandering-the-earth thing.
我去买点吃的 我们继续谈
I'm gonna buy you dinner, and we're gonna talk.
琳赛 我不行
Lindsey, i can't.
不行 唯一能避免流血的方法是答应
No. the only way to avoid bloodshed is to say yes.
放轻松
Relax.
这是一个罪恶的地方
This is a den of iniquity.
我不应该出现在这里
I should not be here.
兄弟 你全力反抗上天
Dude, you full-on rebelled against heaven.
罪恶就当是一个额外补贴
Iniquity is one of the perks.
表演时刻
Showtime.
你好 你叫什么名字？
Hi. what's your name.
卡西
Cass!
他的名字是卡西 你的呢？
His name is cass. what's your name.
纯洁
Chastity.
是不是命运安排什么的？老兄
Is that kismet or what, buddy huh.
很好 他喜欢你 你也喜欢他 所以…
Well, he likes you, and you like him, so…
[希伯来语]
来吧 宝贝
Mm. come on, baby.
听着
Oh, hey. listen.
拿着这个
Take this.
如果她要求信用卡支付 没有
If she asks for a credit card, no.
现在 记住基本常识 知道么？
Now, just stick to the basics, okay.
不要退缩
Do not order off the menu.
跟她去吧 猛男
Go get her, tiger.
别让我推你
Don't make me push you.
干杯
Cheers to you.
滚出我的视线
Get out of my face!
离我远点儿
No! leave me alone!
混蛋 去你妈的 废物
Bastard! screw you, jerk!
我要杀了你
I'll kill you!
你也不是好鸟 天哪
Screw you, too! god!
混球
Ohh! jerk!
你到底做什么了？
What the hell did you do.
我不知道
I don't know.
我只是看着她的眼睛
I just looked at her in the eyes.
告诉她这不是她的错
And told her it wasn't her fault.
她的父亲已经死了
That her father, gene, ran off.
那是因为他讨厌在邮局工作
It was because he hated his job at the post office.
不是吧 大哥
Oh, no, man.
什么？
What.
这里的一切上帝都不会出来干预
This whole industry runs on absent fathers.
这是自然顺序
It's … it's the natural order.
我们该走了 快点儿
We should go. come on.
这太好笑了
What's so funny.
没事
Oh, nothing.
好长时间我没这样大声笑过了
It's been a long time since i've laughed that hard.
真的好长时间了
Oh, it's been more than a long time.
好几年
Years.
所以…
So…
你准备告诉我回到这里的那些人的真实身份
You gonna tell me who those guys back there really were.
不要说是狩猎伙伴
And don't say hunting buddies.
好吧
Okay. um…
我们曾经一起做同一事业
We used to be in the same business together.
什么事业
What business.
你的沙拉怎么样？
How's your salad.
收保护费 你是黑手党
Witness protection, right you're mafia.
我不是黑手党
I'm not mafia.
好 我懂了
Okay. I get it.
我不是想打探你的隐私 我的错
I don't mean to pry. my bad.
我以前和我哥哥一起做事
I used to be in business with my brother.
事实是我还蛮擅长那个工作
Truth is, i was… pretty good at the job.
但我出了一些差错
But… I made some mistakes.
你知道 我做了一些我觉得不好的事
You know, i-i did some stuff i'm not so proud of.
让人受到了伤害
And people got hurt.
很多人
A lot of people.
你磕的什么毒品？
What was your poison.
你说什么？
Sorry.
说吧
Come on.
你对某些东西上瘾了 我熟悉那表情
You were hooked on something. I know the look.
清醒了3年
Three years sober.
你在酒吧工作
You work in a bar.
你也是
So do you.
听着 凯斯
Look, keith …
我不了解你
I don't know you,
我是最后一个给你忠告的人
And i'm the last person to be giving advice,
但我知道
But I do know that…
从来没人做过这样的坏事
No one has ever done anything so bad,
他们不会原谅
They can't be forgiven.
更不会改变
That they can't change.
当油燃烧起来时
When the oil burns,
没有天使敢靠近或是跨过火焰
No angel can touch or pass through the flames,
除非是活得不耐烦了
Or he dies.
明白
Okay.
也就是说我们给他套了个燃烧着圣火的牢狱之笼
So we trap him in a steel cage of holy fire.
不过 问个问题
But, uh, one question …
我们要怎么召唤他降世到这人身上呢
How the hell do we get him here?
通常 天使和他的皮囊之间
There's … well, almost an open phone line…
都会存在着特别的联系
Between a vessel and his angel.
之后就只需要再用对方法就行了
One just has to know how to dial.
[咒语]
我在这儿呢 拉斐尔
I'm here, Raphael.
过来占有我吧 小兔崽子
Come and get me, you little bastard.
就是有那么点儿好奇 大概
Just out of curiosity, what is.
一般我们需要等多久才能等来大天使呢
The average customer wait time to speak to an archangel?
随时都可能
Be ready.
靠 浪费了我一整天的时间
Well, that's a day I'll never get back.
迪恩 慢着
Dean. Wait!
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
拉斐尔
Raphael.
你搞这么多不就是想多出出镜嘛
I mean, I thought you were supposed to be impressive.
结果却把房间搞得黑灯瞎火了
All you do is black out the room?
是这个东海岸都黑灯瞎火才对
And the eastern seaboard.
如果不是遵守圣约要圣怜悯人
It is a testament to my unending mercy.
我早就给你们好看了
That I don't smite you here and now.
不然就是你在信口雌黄
Or maybe you're full of crap.
也许你根本就是在害怕
Maybe you're afraid.
害怕上帝再次将卡西复活
That god will bring Cass back to life again.
并把你好好地教训一顿 你这纸老虎
And smite you, you candy-ass skirt.
随便自我介绍下 我是迪恩
By the way … hi. I'm Dean.
我当然知道你是那位
I know who you are.
而且 还要感谢他 终于让我找到了你
And now, thanks to him, I know where you are.
你不会对他下手
You won't kill him.
更不敢对他下手
You wouldn't dare.
但我可以抓他去见米迦勒
But I will take him to Michael.
哇噢 那 听起来真够吓人的
Well, that…sounds terrifying.
真得很吓人
It does.
但是 我又不得不告诉你
But, uh, I hate to tell you…
我可不会仍你摆布
I'm not going anywhere with you.
相信你还记得撒迦利亚赏你的那个胃癌吧
Surely you remember Zachariah giving you stomach cancer.
当然 那真是 真是让人捧腹不已啊
Yeah. that was … that was hilarious.
没错
Yes, well…
那对我而言不过是雕虫小技
He doesn't have anything close to my imagination.
噢 是吗
Oh, yeah?
我敢说有一件事你肯定压根就没想到
I bet you didn't imagine one thing.
什么
What?
对你的到来我们早有准备 你这杂碎
We knew you were coming, you stupid son of a bitch.
嘿 别看我 是他的主意
Hey, don't look at me. it was his idea.
他在哪儿
Where is he?
上帝吗
God?
你真没听说吗
Didn't you hear?
他已经死了 卡西迪奥
He's dead, Castiel.
早就死了
Dead.
已经打烊了
Bar's closed.
你是不是有事该告诉我啊 萨姆
Is there something you want to tell me, Sam?
啥
What?
没有啊
No.
你确定
You sure about that?
我 我不
I-I don't…
老天
Geez.
你没事儿吧
Are you okay?
雷吉和史蒂夫呢
Where are Reggie and Steve?
史蒂夫挺好的
Oh, Steve's good.
他 嗯
He's, uh…
正内脏外露地躺在街对面那间便利店外
His guts are laying roadside outside the hawley five-and-dime.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
道歉有个屁用 萨姆
"sorry" don't cut it, Sam.
你想要我说什么
What do you want me to say?
实话
The truth.
好吧 既然这样
Okay. fine.
那就我先开个头好了
Let me give you some of my own, then.
我们进城 来猎捕一直追踪的那个恶魔
We go into town, we capture ourselves a demon,
然而等着我们确超过了十个
And we get jumped by 10 more.
史蒂夫就这么死于非命了
Steve bought it.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
再道几次歉也无济于事 萨姆
Saying it twice don't make it so, Sam.
但是知道吗 有个恶魔 他
But you see, this demon, he, uh…
他告诉了我们一些事儿
He told us things.
疯狂的事儿 和你有关 萨姆
Crazy things. things about you, Sam.
恶魔们骗你们的
Demons lie.
是吗
Yeah?
我在最后一次问你
I'm gonna ask you one last time.
说实话
The truth.
立刻
Now!
琳赛
Lindsey!
怎么回事啊
What's going on?
没别的解释了
There's no other explanation.
只可能是他死了
He's gone for good.
有吗
Am I.
还记得20世纪的事吗
Do you remember the 20th century.
21世纪有见得比那时好吗
Think the 21st is going any better.
你觉得如果上帝还健在
You think god would have let any of that happen.
他会让这些灾难发生吗
If he were alive.
正如你所说
Oh, yeah.
那么又是谁赋予人类下三滥招数
Well, then who invented the chinese basket trick.
小心说话
Careful.
娃儿 你谈论的可是上帝
That's my father you're talking about, boy.
是啊 不就是那个
Yeah, who would be so proud.
以狗屁天启而沾沾自喜的混蛋嘛
To know that his sons started the frigging apocalypse.
他不仅逃跑还玩失踪
Who ran off and disappeared.
留下一群无头苍蝇以及孤立无援的世界
Who left no instructions and a world to run.
那么上帝只是潜逃消失了
So daddy ran away and disappeared.
他该不会碰巧在邮局当差吧
He didn't happen to work for the post office, did he.
这对你来说很有趣吗
This is funny to you.
你当下可是活在一个无神世界里
You're living in a godless universe.
那么
And.
他不在班时 你和其他天使
What … you and the other kids.
就只是打算在人间开个天启吗
Just decide to throw an apocalypse while he's gone.
我们倦了
We're tired.
只想结束这一切
We just want it to be over.
只想
We just want…
重回天堂
Paradise.
那么上帝一死 你做了头
So, what … god dies and makes you the boss,
你以为就能为所欲为了吗
And you think you can do whatever you want.
正是
Yes.
我们的确能随心所欲
And whatever we want, we get.
别这样好吗 咱好好说话
Let's just take it easy, okay.
把刀放下
Put the knife down.
是真的
It's true.
恶魔说的都是真的
What the demon said … it's all true.
继续说
Keep going.
有何区别吗
Why.
你会不那么讨厌我
Are you gonna hate me any less.
还是我会不那么厌恶自己
Am I gonna hate myself any less.
你到底想怎样
What do you want.
我想听你说出来
I want to hear you say it.
是我干的
I did it.
天启是我打开的
I started the apocalypse.
要是上帝真死了 我又是怎么复活的
If god is dead, why have I returned.
谁让我重生的
Who brought me back.
你是否曾想过是路西法救了你
Did it ever occur to you that maybe lucifer raised you.
不可能
No.
好好想想
Think about it.
他需要所有能找到的堕落天使
He needs all the rebellious angels he can find.
你知道这意味着什么
You know it adds up.
我们走
Let's go.
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
我警告你
I'm warning you.
别把我留这儿
Do not leave me here.
我会找到你的
I will find you.
也许有一天你能找到我
Maybe one day.
但今天 你是我们的手下败将
But today, you're my little bitch.
听到他说的了吧
What he said.
那是什么
What is that.
你觉得呢
What do you think it is.
这是恶魔之血 小萨姆
It's go juice, sammy boy.
离我远点
Get that away from me.
离你远点 那可是大错特错的
Away from you wrong.
这可是为你量身定做的
This is for you.
见鬼 要是那恶魔撒谎
Hell, if that demon wasn't right as rain.
那你就都喝光试试 孩子
Down the hatch, son.
你这个疯子
You're insane.
听着 照我说的做
Look, here's what's gonna happen.
喝了这玩意 然后变身
You're gonna drink this, hulk out,
把那些杀了我好友的恶魔
And you're gonna waste every one of those demon scum.
都杀光光
That killed my best friend.
不然她就得死
Or she dies.
你不会这么做的
You wouldn't do that.
看到你好友的死却换来这样的结局真是有趣
It's funny how watching your best friend die changes that.
快喝了 你想喝的 萨姆
Come on. You know you want it, Sam.
拿过去喝光吧
Just reach out and take it.
好啦 也没那么糟吧
There. Was that really so bad.
滚
Go.
别以为我们不会杀回来了
Don't think we won't be back.
别以为我不会杀回来
Don't think I won't be here.
伙计 你没事吧
Hey, man, you okay.
听着 我多想告诉你
Look, I'll be the first to tell you.
那小骚货在撒谎 但
That this little crusad of yours is nuts but…
我知道失去父亲的滋味
I do know a little something about missing fathers.
你什么意思
What do you mean.
我是说有时候我到处找我父亲时
I mean there were times when I was looking for my dad.
虽然理智告诉我他已经死了
When…all logic said that he was dead.
但我知道 在我内心深处
But I knew, in my heart…
总感觉他还活着
That he was still alive.
谁会在乎某些忍者神龟的屁话 卡西
Who cares what some ninja turtle says, cass.
重要的是你怎么想
What do you believe.
我觉得他还健在
I believe he's out there.
很好
Good.
那就去找到他
Then go find him.
你怎么办
What about you?
我怎么办
What about me?
怎么说呢
I don't know.
说实话
Honestly,
我很好
I'm good.
想不到我会这么说 但我很好
I can't believe I'm saying that, but I am.
我 我真的很好
I'm… I'm really good.
和你弟弟分开也很好
Even without your brother?
和我弟弟分开尤其好
Especially without my brother.
我是说 我为那个混蛋
I mean, I spent so much time.
操了那么多心
Worrying about the son of a bitch.
你看 我跟你在一起的这24小时
I mean, I've had more fun with you in the past 24 hours.
比跟萨姆在一起的几年都要开心
Than I've had with Sam in years.
不过你也不是什么有趣的人
And you're not that much fun.
真讽刺
It's funny.
你知道我对家人多投入
You know, I've been so chained to my family.
可是现在一个人了
But now that I'm alone…
我很开心
Hell, I'm happy.
这么说
So…
这就是你现在的生活
This is your life now?
你觉得你可以一直这样
You think you can just live forever.
像鸵鸟一样把头埋在沙土里的躲下去吗
With your head buried in the sand?
我爱你 杰西
I love you, Jess.
上帝知道我有多么想念你
God knows how much I miss you, too.
但是你错了
But you're wrong.
人是可以变的
People can change.
我们当抱有希望
There is reason for hope.
不 萨姆
No, Sam.
没有希望了
There isn't.
你为什么如此确定
How can you be so sure?
因为你释放了我
Because you freed me.
猜对了
That's right.
你知道我是谁
You know who I am.
路西法
Lucifer.
找你可真难哪 萨姆
You are a hard one to find, Sam.
比大部分人类都难找
Harder than most humans.
我想你是不会告诉我你在哪里了
I don't suppose you'll tell me where you are.
你要做什么
What do you want with me?
多亏了你 我才能来到人间
Thanks to you, I walk the earth.
我想送你一件礼物
I want to give you a gift.
我想给你所有的东西
I want to give you everything.
我不想要你的东西
I don't want anything from you.
我很抱歉 萨姆 真心的
I'm so sorry, Sam. I-I really am.
但这个尼克只是个临时替代品
But Nick here is just an improvisation.
并非首选
Plan B.
他只是能容纳我 勉强维持不会自燃而已
He can barely contain me without spontaneously combusting.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
不然你以为你为什么会在那个礼拜堂里
Why do you think you were in that chapel?
只有你才能做到 萨姆
You're the one, Sam.
你是我的皮囊
You're my vessel.
我真正的皮囊
My true vessel.
不可能
No.
是真的
Yes.
不可能
No.
这绝不可能
That'll never happen.
我很抱歉 但一切已注定
I'm sorry, but it will.
我会找到你
I will find you.
到时候
And when I do…
你会同意我进入的
You will let me in.
我很确定
I'm sure of it.
你需要我同意
You need my consent?
当然了 我是天使嘛
Of course. I'm an angel.
我宁可杀死我自己也不会同意的
I will kill myself before letting you in.
我会把你复活的
And I'll just bring you back.
萨姆
Sam.
你让我的心都碎了
My heart breaks for you.
你肩上的担子
The weight on your shoulders.
你做过的那些事
What you've done.
你还要做的那些事
What you still have to do.
都不是其他人能够承受的
It is more than anyone could bear.
如果有其他的办法
If there was some other way…
可惜没有
But there isn't.
我绝不会对你撒谎
I will never lie to you.
也不会骗你
I will never trick you.
你会答应我的
But you will say yes to me.
你错了
You're wrong.
我没错
I'm not.
我想我比你更了解你自己
I think I know you better than you know yourself.
为什么是我
Why me?
因为舍你其谁呢 萨姆
Because it had to be you, Sam.
这非你莫属
It always had to be you.